{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "1. Which number is the answer to the Universe?",
      "answers": [
        "a. 40",
        "b. 30",
        "c. 52",
        "d. 42"
      ],
      "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "2. What is the name of the main elf character in LOTR?",
        "answers": [
          "a. Gimly",
          "b. Aragor",
          "c. Legolas",
          "d. Smeagle"
        ],
        "correct": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "3. Who is the first man to climb Everest?",
        "answers": [
          "a. Edmund Hillary",
          "b. Tommy Heinrich",
          "c. Hristo Prodanov",
          "d. Earl Denman"
        ],
        "correct": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "4. What year were held the first Modern Olimpic games?",
        "answers": [
            "a. 1643",
            "b. 1949",
            "c. 1350",
            "d. 1896"
        ],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "5. How high is the tallest building in the world? (2018)",
        "answers": [
            "a. 759 M.",
            "b. 828 M.",
            "c. 632 M.",
            "d. 900 M."
        ],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "6. Point out the three car brands, which are entirely Asian-made?",
        "answers": [
            "a. Lexus, Nissan, Ford",
            "b. Birkin, Laraki, Kiira",
            "c. Denza, Honda, Mazda",
            "d. Abarth, Mitsubishi, Everus"
        ],
        "correct": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "7. Who invented the bycicle in its first two-wheel form?",
        "answers": [
            "a. Giovanni Fontana",
            "b. Karl von Drais",
            "c. Pierre Michaux",
            "d. Marius Olivier"
        ],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "8. How many people play the popular computer game League of Legends (LoL) all over the World?",
        "answers": [
            "a. 58 Million",
            "b. 76 Million",
            "c. 113 Million",
            "d. 81 Million"
        ],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "9. What period (in years) did the Bulgarian monarch tsar Simeon I rule the country?",
        "answers": [
            "a. From 893 To 927 AD",
            "b. From 897 To 941 AD",
            "c. From 880 To 900 AD",
            "d. From 887 To 917 AD"
        ],
        "correct": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "10. Can a Person jump over 8.5 meters long?",
        "answers": [
            "a. Yes and this already happened",
            "b. No, no one cant",
            "c. Yes but its never been recorded",
            "d. No but they were pretty close"
        ],
        "correct": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "11. We know that the number PI has really a lot of numbers after the decimal point. We know that it starts with 3.1415. What is the next (5-th) number?",
        "answers": [
            "a. 4",
            "b. 3",
            "c. 7",
            "d. 9"
        ],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "12. Where was StarBucks founded (in which city)?",
        "answers": [
            "a. Portland",
            "b. Denver",
            "c. Seattle",
            "d. Baltimore"
        ],
        "correct": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "13. At what age did the oldest person in the world die?",
        "answers": [
            "a. 115",
            "b. 120",
            "c. 117",
            "d. 122"
        ],
        "correct": 3
      }
  ]
}